Pass it!
Stop him now!
The world inside a photo is the past.
Anything you change there will usually warp space and time, with one exception.
And what's that?
The timeline is made up of important nodes.
You might accidentally alter something before one of these points, but you're in the clear if the critical event still happens.
History will play out as it's supposed to.
It was the most horrible day of my life.
I failed a friend, missed my first love, and got in an awful fight with my mom.
If the important node is altered, everything after that is changed, rewritten.
It didn't take too long to realize something has changed in the back of my mind.
Your eyes, there ain't nowhere left to hide behind.
Time no longer flew like it was, when the flash froze everything before.
Without you, I don't know if I could take this road.
And I'm about to lose my mind.
Every minute that I die, back in time.
Every single existence rewinds.
Some physical pain in this eye dry.
All mine.
All the hottest and the smiles never faded.
I know you'll be by my side when we make it.
Come back from the times.
Back in time.
Time back in time.
under pressure who would have thought yeah what kind of defense was that you just lost to a bunch
of backwoods amateurs that kid the hell where'd he come from no way he's a benchwarmer you killed
it seriously what a pass uh hey dude are you okay come on say something
all right pictures that'll kill time no flash turn it off
offensive charging from long young blue did i change the timeline
everything out of that has changed rewritten
yo new guy you feel like playing some ball pass it back let's see if you've got any game
as long as the note is altered future stays the same
blue hey it's still there
hey you good i think that wind might have overwhelmed the poor guy game like that blow
anyone's mine shin chow don't touch me
cap i'm sorry i need some space
where are you damn it say something
no don't
there you are where have you been you bastard i was about to jump out of the picture
the client wrote his wishes on a note chow ling misplaced it
i think i found it look at you all worried for a change honestly it's nice to see
wait was this some kind of lesson i wish i was that clever you did just rewrite the ending
of the game but the big note that's still unchanged
huh which note's that hey chen here don't forget your camera just because you won the match
i guess i got too excited what's next huh will we be going up against other teams soon and the gym
they won't tear it down since we won right yeah well hate to tell you this kid but today didn't matter
they already plan to tear this place down it was decided long before the game in the end to them studying is more important than basketball
hey cap i bet we'll get to play a big county school next don't you think that'll be awesome
a few more wins and the town will start coming out to cheer us on maybe they can help us repair the gym too
new floors and lights they'll be incredible imagine we're going to be so much more legit now
i can't wait yeah maybe i should tell them the truth now that way at least i can break the news softly
thanks coach i told you i'm just a chem teacher seriously what's your problem today
keep it together you've barely even begun don't forget your mission
i'm just delivering messages shouldn't be too hard sure but before that you have to get lu ho ben back
home i left my legs in the gym this hill's gonna kill me why did it have to be a bike a scooter would
have been so much better hey uh stop if you're tired no way i'm just now getting my stride
sounds like you're doing just fine good work you can say the client's words now
about time i'm seriously about a faint
hey man you're so good at basketball why didn't you tell us i was worried about
making you the team's backup pick but you killed it cap there's something i want to say
all right
Stop right there!
You snuck off to play basketball again
when you should have been studying, didn't you?
Oh gosh, what happened to your leg?
Don't tell me it's broken.
Little sisters don't get to guilt their older brothers.
You're not learning anything playing that dumb game
and you certainly won't make money off it.
That girl is our client's first love.
She's also the subject of our second mission.
Yeah, I figured it was her
given the way his body just reacted.
You on my brother's team too?
That's weird.
Never seen you before.
Oh, wait.
I barely recognized you without the glasses on.
So, did you finally learn how to see or what?
How about that?
They got trashed while I was playing.
For real?
Were you on the court today or fighting?
Because one of you can barely see
and the other's got a busted knee.
Okay, okay.
That's enough lecturing.
I swear, you sound exactly like your mom.
Oh, hey.
How about a picture, huh?
A picture?
What, was today that good?
Yep.
And a happy day is worth remembering.
Geez, I realize you've been studying so much,
but did you really forget how to smile?
Come on, big grin.
For me.
One, two, three.
Busted knee.
Now you two.
Smile with the ace, sis.
The what?
You should have seen this guy earlier.
He was a dunking master.
Impossible.
He's basically my height.
Well, yeah, I guess I kind of killed it.
Learned it from watching cartoons.
Hey, watch yourself.
Try not to show off too much.
Don't sell yourself short.
Come on.
Oh, no.
I'm all sweaty from the bike ride.
Nobody wants that picture.
Take the photo.
You nerd.
Get over there and smile.
Hurry it up.
Hey, what's the deal with the distance?
Scooch in, would you?
Don't even hand down.
One, two, three.
Team can't see.
Finally home.
Thanks.
You were a big help.
Oh, no problem.
He barely weighs a thing.
See you guys later.
Not so fast.
Hey, walk him to the road, yeah?
Oh, wow.
Her feelings are written all over her face.
How could he have possibly missed that?
Don't question it.
You're just there to deliver his words.
After her, there's one left.
His heart's about to beat out of his chest.
He wanted to talk to her so bad.
Why didn't they end up together?
By the way, you look really nice without your glasses.
You have really pretty eyes.
Whoa.
She made the first move.
What am I supposed to do?
Um, do you know much about my family?
Sure.
Sort of, from what your brother told me.
Yeah, well, he's my half-brother.
My father wants me to move to the city with him
so I can study there after the high school entrance exam.
What do you think?
Hey, line.
What should I say?
Hey.
Pinky promise.
Yeah, you got it. I promise.
Lu, was it really okay to tell her something like that? Don't you think that promise will screw up the timeline?
No. The future won't change unless the critical note does.
Right. If you say it's cool.
Did I raise an idiot? What were you thinking? And where are your glasses? You were supposed to be studying.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? That's great. Perfect. You keep it up and you'll turn out just like your father. Kitchen, right now!
Right. I'll …
Take a seat.
So much food. There's just us two. Such a waste.
That's not true. Your father might show up. He never warns me and then blames me if there's not enough to eat. Better to cook.
In case he decides to come home, you know? Besides, it's not a waste if you eat it.
Don't get distracted by the meal. You still have to fight with her.
What? Is it not good?
I saw Cap's sister earlier and she told me she's going to study in the city soon. So I'm just wondering when I'll be able to go too.
Eat that. I took all the meat off for you. You'll like it.
I planned to work in the city anyway. I could get a job there. And study, of course. That would …
Then go! You know where the door is. I know both of you would rather be there than here at home. Never mind your poor mother. I'll live.
Ever since your dad left to work for that tabloid, I never know where he is. He doesn't call. I mean, he could be dead for all I know.
For years, he spent his days taking photos of other people. But when was the last time he took one of his family?
I knew it. You're exactly like he is. Wasted talent and just as selfish. Do I not matter?
If you want to move so bad, rise to the top of your class. Get into a good school, then settle in the city and bring us with you.
I don't want to say anything that will hurt her. Then finish the job quickly.
And you're sure repeating after you is okay? Don't worry. The eventual result won't change no matter how this argument plays out.
Let's go!
Something seems off.
Is that really all we needed to do for this mission?
No use worrying about it now.
Messages are delivered.
Our job's done.
Can I at least stuff myself?
I worked super hard today.
I swear, nothing beats a homemade dinner.
Thanks, but you better have saved room for some noodles.
There's no way I can eat any more.
Mercy, please.
I'm bursting here.
Be a good boy and finish the bowl.
Sorry, it's impossible.
Gotta run.
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
Today is the 12th of May.
You know, your father's birthday.
We have to celebrate with birthday noodles, even if he's not here.
Wait, what year is it?
What?
Are you feeling all right?
It's still 2008.
I'm coming.
Jeez.
Those ears swirly.
They're gone.
Hey, what's wrong?
Everything all right?
The news.
There was a big earthquake.
It killed a bunch of people last night.
And I...
I don't know what to do.
Were my mom and dad caught in it?
What if they don't come back?
What if I never see them again?
Don't worry.
They were probably nowhere near there.
I'm sure they'll come back home.
What if they're both dead and now I'm all alone?
I miss them already.
I miss them so much.
Hun, why are you staring at the table like that?
Hello?
Good to show.
Are you all right?
Say something.
The mission is over.
Get out!
So that's it.
Come with me, son.
The reason you let me change things.
It doesn't matter what I tell them because they're all doomed.
They die in the quake.
The timeline is made up of important nodes.
You might accidentally alter something before one of these points,
but you're in the clear if the critical event still happens.
History will play out as it's supposed to.
All three of them.
Right?
Pinky promise.
Yeah, you got it.
I promise.
Listen to me, Auntie.
You have to stay here, okay?
I'll be back later.
Huh?
Hey, wouldn't you call me?
Auntie?
What's with you?
It's dark outside.
Where are you going?
Stop this.
You can't save them.
They are already dead.
Come back now before you make a terrible mistake.
Listen to me.
Death is an important node that must not be changed.
No matter how hard this is, you can't alter their fates.
The chaos that would cause.
Dink, damn it!
The future that we now know could completely disappear.
I got lost in the street and I'm living in.
Or maybe I should just quit overthinking.
無意識看了看我的右手
難落也掠過了我的胸口
沒來得及說藏著天候
我目光怎麼又被偷走
You should really stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinking about it
Why your mind overcarded
脱離現實的夢境華未紀錶
始終的我需要ить壓才能自暴
So stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinkin' bout it while your mind overclouded
In this time, the fear of stopping
I understand the amount of anxiety that I can use
Stop thinkin' bout it
Stop stop thinkin' bout it while your mind overclouded
Yeah